Oh, if it isn't Mrs. Dead-To-Me.
(Steph:)Hello, Howard.
- Sheldon?
- I'm sorry, you violated...
(Sheldon:)...the terms of your metaphor
by acknowledging her existence. I'm out.
(Leonard:)He just won't listen to me.
Okay, well, I guess
it'll just be the three of us then.
- Yeah. Lisa's gonna be disappointed.
STEPHANIE: Yeah.
(Howard:)Lisa?
(Steph:)Yeah, my roommate.
She just went through a bad breakup.
(Steph:)I thought she might like to meet
somebody fun like you.
(Howard:)Leonard, Stephanie, you're alive.
It's a miracle.
(Howard:)So anyway, Lisa,
I just wanted to tell you again...
(Howard:)...how much I enjoyed the other night,
and again, I'm sorry for how it ended.
(Howard:)But again,
if you could let me know about Friday...
(Howard:)...my mother needs a head count
so she can know how big a brisket to get.
(Leonard:)Howard. Look at this.
[MAN SPEAKING INDISTINCTLY ON TV]
(Howard:)Anyway, call me. It's Howard.
ANNOUNCER [ON TV]: It's unclear how
the Mars rover got into the crevice...
...but one thing's certain:
(Voice from TV:)The data which it has sent back
contain the first clear indications...
(Voice from TV:)...that there may have been life on Mars.
(Voice from TV:)It's a scientific discovery...
(Voice from TV:)...that has staggering implications
for all mankind.
(Voice from TV:)Unfortunately,
we'll never know who's responsible.
(Howard:)Son of a bitch.